PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

SHAFINA RIFDHAYANTI ZEIN

UNDERGRADUATE STUDENT OF ELECTRICAL **ENGINEERING**

Personal Summary

Undergraduate student focused on technological developments, especially on electronic equipment from the electrical engineering department of Brawijaya University. Experience in writing and innovating will have a big impact for me to deepen my knowledge and form a good personality Especially in being a disciplined person, hard worker and able to communicate with various types of people.







shafinarzein@gmail.com



http://linkedin.com/in/shafinarzein



+62 821 3935 6317



@shfn.zein

Education

ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING - 2019/2023

Concentration in Electronic Engineering

Engineering Skills

- AutoCAD
- Proteus
- Inventor
- MATLAB
- EAGLE

Experience

• INTERNSHIP | 2021

PT Wijaya Karya Beton. TBK

Having a practical work experience at PT Wijaya Karya Beton. TBK unit Kejapanan Gempol Pasuruan Which is placed on equipment maintenance and controlling tools

ASSISTANT LABORATORY | 2020 - NOW

Digital system Laboratory

Assisting of Electrical Engineering student to do their practicum in in order to have competence in assembling and compiling electronic systems and processing discrete systems

DIVISIONAL STAFF OF RESEARCH AND TECHNOLOGY | 2021 - NOW

BEM Teknik Universitas Brawijaya

Having experience being responsible for PKM in the Faculty of Engineering and Branding the achievement of the Faculty of Engineering

• DEVELOPER / CLOUD COMPUTING | 2022 - NOW

Bangkit Academy by Google, GoTo, Traveloka

Online bootcamp and skill learning for Cloud Computing and Back-End Development for University Student

Achievement

TOP 3TH | JUNE 2021

Electrical Equipment Design PLN ICE (Innovation & Competition in Electricity)

FINALIS DEMODAY PERTAMUDA | AUGUST 2021

PT. PERTAMINA (PERSERO)

3RD WINNER NATIONAL ESSAY | AUGUST 2021

Universitas Lambung Mangkurat

